{
    "subject": "resource/Mura,_Barcelona",
    "predicate": "ontology/timeZone",
    "object": "resource/Central_European_Summer_Time",
    "human_readable": "Mura, Barcelona is in Central European Summer Time.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9629386067390442,
            "question": "Is Barcelona part of Central European Summer Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8646970987319946,
            "question": "Does Mura observe the same time zone as Barcelona during summer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7928944230079651,
            "question": "Would someone in Barcelona experience sunrise earlier or later during Central European Summer Time compared to standard time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7445240616798401,
            "question": "What time zone is Barcelona in during the summer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6315560340881348,
            "question": "What is the name of the time zone that applies to Barcelona in the summer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5942630767822266,
            "question": "During which season does Central European Summer Time apply?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4483869969844818,
            "question": "Where is Mura located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3269507586956024,
            "question": "What type of time zone system does Barcelona use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27251866459846497,
            "question": "How many hours ahead is Central European Summer Time compared to Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23333069682121277,
            "question": "What is the time difference between Barcelona and a place in Eastern Standard Time?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mura, Barcelona is in Central European Summer Time.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1822_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many hours ahead is Central European Summer Time compared to Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1822_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of time zone system does Barcelona use?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1822_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Mura located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1822_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1822_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1822_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1822_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1822_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1822_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1822_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1822_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1822_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1822_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1822_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states \"Mura is located in the time zone Central European Summer Time.\"  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe triple states that Mura, Barcelona is in Central European Summer Time. According to document `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1822/re-ranker-msmarco/73.txt`, it's mentioned that \"Mura is located in the time zone Central European Summer Time.\" Therefore, this statement is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information states that \"Mura is located in the time zone Central European Summer Time.\" This supports the query that Mura, Barcelona is in Central European Summer Time."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n    }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}